viralsection.com 2016-04-04

# Privacy Policy

At ViralSection.com we make sure that all the information you store with us is private and confidential. We never sell your data with anyone and hate spammer as much as you do.

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, ViralSection.com will learn certain information about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

**Advertising Policy**

We also Use a Third Party Advertising network called Google AdSense and this party may place DART Cookies in your Browser to know about your personal preferences to target the ads more efficiently. We have no access to or control over these cookies which are used by third-party advertisers. If you feel that you want to opt out of this, then you can do so here – http://www.google.com/privacy/ads

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use only your email information to notify you for new posts on this website and that too only if you subscribe to us through Google FeedBurner platform. We assure that your email information is safe with us and is not shared with a third-party at any cost.

**Note About Children**

Since we do not host mature content, children are also eligible to use our web site. This website is safe for person with any age including children.

**How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

ViralSection.com may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, ViralSection.com uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
